# Saumya Satpathy

#### **OBJECTIVE:**

A professional with years of experience bringing planning and problem-solving abilities. Organized and systematic with natural relationship-building and leadership talents. Highlymotivated employee with desire to take on new challenges. Strong work ethic, adaptability, and exceptional interpersonal skills. Adept at working effectively unsupervised quickly and mastering new skills.

#### **SKILLS:**

- Teamwork
- Decision Making
- Customer Retention
- Interpersonal Skills
- Logical Thinking
- Performance Improvement
- Customer Service Management

#### ADDRESS:

BANGALORE-560041

# PHONE:

7978384556

#### **EMAIL**

s.satpathy11@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# FEB 2024- CURRENT

# Community Lead

- Overseeing mid-level & associate community managers.
- Responsible for coordinating initiatives and strategies, setting and operationalizing community objectives.
- Collaborated with team members on projects related to community development and growth.
- Addressed and resolved client inquiries and issues promptly, maintaining high levels of customer satisfaction and fostering long-term relationships.
- Monitored and updated CRM (Alfred & Helios) records to maintain accurate client information and track sales progress.

#### OCT 2023-DEC 2023

# Internship | Kidvento Education and Research Pvt Ltd

- Communication, Research & Analysis
- Handling leads from Central Region
- Actively part of customer success by solving gueries.

#### FEB 2023-SEP 2023

# Sales Manager | BuildNext IT Enabled Company

- Have developed and implemented effective sales strategies to achieve company objectives.
- Helped in identifying the new business opportunities, building and maintaining relationships with potential and existing clients.
- Market analysis to understand customers preferences and pitching the right product.
- Utilized CRM (HubSpot) to analyze customer data and sales patterns.

#### MAY 2022-DEC 2022

# Pre-Sales Consultant | Livspace Home Interiors

- Develop strong relationship with potential customers and organization.
- Working as part of a team to create strategies for the sales.
- Handling particularly Lucknow, Jaipur & Ahmedabad, cities to achieve targets.
- Collaborated with sales team to devise strategies for positioning products against competitors.

# JUN 2020-MAY 2022

# Sales Manager | Walnut Publication

• Leading, trained and motivated the team to achieve the numbers.

# LINKEDIN

http://www.linkedin.com/in/sa umya-satpathy-73550090

# **HOBBIES:**

- Music
- Yoga
- Designing
- Crafting
- Image Processing

- Identify and pursue new business opportunities and partnerships to expand the publication reach and revenue streams.
- Recruit new creative candidates for expanding knowledge, growth and need for training & delivering it.
- Maintaining & improving relationships with the client.
- Delivered sales presentations focused on offerings and unique advantages over competitors.

# JUN 2018-MAY 2020

# Soft Skill & Life Skill Trainer -cum- Executive Operations | Helen O' Grady International

- Responsible for helping and finding solutions
- Train students for personal, self-management, social skills
- Prepared learning materials & planning activities
- Handles a team to carry the process & maintain the channel.
- Communicated with managements & provided information.
- Reviewed files, records, and other documents to obtain information to respond to requests.

# FEB 2016-AUG 2016

# Project Assistant | KIIT University

 Developed processes and procedures to ensure efficient workflow of projects.

# **EDUCATION**

M-TECH (CSIS)- KIIT UNIVERSITY

Jan 2016

B-TECH (CS)- HITECH INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY

Jan 2012

#### TRAINING-AWARDS

- Attended a seminar "Re-imagine Education- A Global Approach in 21st Century", collaborated with World Trade Centre.
- Received a Certificate for Effective Communication from the Head Trainer of South Africa.
- Received a Certificate for the completion of internship on Marketing and Sales from IFORTIS WORLDWIDE.
- Completed a short-certified course of Management Skills-2023.

#### **DISCLAIMER**

I, hereby declare that the above details are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.